<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8' standalone='no'?>
<doxygen xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="compound.xsd" version="1.8.15">
  <compounddef id="indexpage" kind="page">
    <compoundname>index</compoundname>
    <title>Rubeus</title>
    <briefdescription>
    </briefdescription>
    <detaileddescription>
<para><image type="html" name="rubeus_dark.png"></image>
</para><para><heading level="1">Introduction</heading>
</para><para><ref refid="namespace_rubeus" kindref="compound">Rubeus</ref> is a cross-platform 2D game engine written in C++17.</para><para>It is specifically designed for people who are new to game development. <ref refid="namespace_rubeus" kindref="compound">Rubeus</ref> derives its work flow from a lot of popular game engines which will be clearer if you follow the <ulink url="https://github.com/sdslabs/Rubeus/wiki">Getting Start guide</ulink>.</para><para>The reason for incorporating a simple workflow helps <ref refid="namespace_rubeus" kindref="compound">Rubeus</ref> in being used for smaller projects which still resemble the work done in the industry as well as introducing people to the culture and thought process of game programming.</para><para>If you want to contribute to the documentation, then have a look at <ulink url="https://github.com/sdslabs/Rubeus/tree/master/docs">our README for the Rubeus documentation source</ulink>. <hruler/>
</para><para><heading level="1">How to use this Documentation?</heading>
</para><para>The <ref refid="namespace_rubeus" kindref="compound">Rubeus</ref> Documentation is supposed to only be treated as the API documentation. This is probably not a good place to start if you want to start building a game with <ref refid="namespace_rubeus" kindref="compound">Rubeus</ref>. We have our <ulink url="https://github.com/sdslabs/Rubeus/wiki">Getting Start guide</ulink> for it. This is for those people who are interested in knowing what class structure <ref refid="namespace_rubeus" kindref="compound">Rubeus</ref> uses and reveal extra features that <ref refid="namespace_rubeus" kindref="compound">Rubeus</ref> provides, which you may not see through Intellisense or code completion.</para><para>Use the <bold>Search</bold> option at the top right hand corner to search for items.</para><para><simplesect kind="warning"><para>Remember, all <ref refid="namespace_rubeus" kindref="compound">Rubeus</ref> class names start with &apos;R&apos; and all Awerere class names start with &apos;A&apos;. Hotkeys for searching are <computeroutput>Tab</computeroutput> and <computeroutput>T</computeroutput> keys.</para></simplesect>
<heading level="1">How to use it?</heading>
</para><para>The <ulink url="https://github.com/sdslabs/Rubeus/wiki">Getting Start guide</ulink> should set you up with initialising <ref refid="namespace_rubeus" kindref="compound">Rubeus</ref> for either local use or development. We recommend giving a read to the other articles present there to know what all <ref refid="namespace_rubeus" kindref="compound">Rubeus</ref> is capable of.</para><para><heading level="1">I have some questions</heading>
</para><para>For general FAQs, we have prepared answers to some basic questions <ulink url="https://github.com/sdslabs/Rubeus/">in our README present here</ulink>. If you have any further doubts, you can reach out to us at <ulink url="chat.sdslabs.co">chat.sdslabs.co</ulink>. We will be setting up a communication server (probably on Gitter, Discord, Slack, or IRC) in the near future. Until then don&apos;t hesitate to ping us.</para><para><heading level="1">Wait, where&apos;s the GUI?</heading>
</para><para>There is no GUI for now. We have developed <ulink url="https://github.com/sdslabs/broCLI">broCLI</ulink> which an CLI tool to generate project files for <ref refid="namespace_rubeus" kindref="compound">Rubeus</ref> and it gives you everything you need to start making your game. Follow the <ulink url="https://github.com/sdslabs/Rubeus/wiki">Getting Start guide</ulink> to know how to use <ulink url="https://github.com/sdslabs/broCLI">broCLI</ulink>.</para><para>This is the official <ref refid="namespace_rubeus" kindref="compound">Rubeus</ref> Engine Documentation. Head over to <ulink url="./pages.html">Pages</ulink> for specific API documentation. <hruler/>
</para><para><heading level="1">Developers</heading>
</para><para>Created by SDSLabs, IIT Roorkee 2018. <ulink url="sdslabs.co">sdslabs.co</ulink> </para>    </detaileddescription>
  </compounddef>
</doxygen>
